

# Muhammad Zidan Fikri Akromy

Jember, East Java, Indonesia

zidanf648@gmail.com

linkedin.com/in/mzidanfa

# Summary

I am a fresh graduate of Profesional Apothecary from University of Jember with GPA 3,84. I have experience internship as apothecary assistant in drugstore for 1 month and pharmaceutical industry for 2 months. I have a good stock of knowledge about GMP and can work with teams and individuals, and can adapt to new environments. I am also interested about front end web development.

# **Experience**

## Student Internship

PT Intijaya Meta Ratna Pharmindo

Apr 2022 - May 2022 (2 months)

- Make an update about specification validation work instruction
- Checking and correcting about batch packaging records and batch production records
- Making reports on the destruction of raw materials, packaging materials, finished products, and documents
- Making renewal of major and minor variations of drug registration

## Independent Study

**Progate** 

Mar 2022 - Apr 2022 (2 months)



#### **Laboratory Assistant**

University of Jember

Feb 2021 - Aug 2021 (7 months)

Assistant lecturer in Pharmacy Biology Laboratories about Phytopharmaceutical

#### **Apothecary Internship**

Zora Farma Apotek

Dec 2020 - Dec 2020 (1 month)

- Perform clinical services such as prescription screening, drug dispensing, information counseling and education.
- Perform medication and drug information services for 10 patients every day
- Planning and procuring drugs to PBF every day
- Help increase pharmacy turnover up to IDR 3,000,000 every day

#### **Education**



#### **University of Jember**

Pharmacist Professional Degree, Pharmacist Professional Study Program, Pharmacy



## University of Jember

Bachelor of Pharmacy - BPharm, Pharmacy

Aug 2017 - Jul 2021

Graduated on time, was given responsibility as laboratory assistant for Phytopharmacy practicun. Also, was active in the Lingkar Journalistic Organization of the Faculty of Pharmacy, University of Jember for the 2019-2020 period as a External Division.

## **Licenses & Certifications**



Front End Developer (Html, Css, JavaScript) - Kementerian Komunikasi dan

Informatika Republik Indonesia FGA/2022/1730/149173029100-1555



Laboratory Assistant - University of Jember

2070/UN25.13/LL/2021

## **Skills**

Good Manufacturing Practice (GMP) • Mentoring • Quality Assurance • Quality Control • Herbal Medicine • Video Editing • Communication • Time Management • Teamwork • Data Entry